Uh... This is a...pizza.
Okay, go.
It's a go, Yata.
- Yo! - Yo!
You're here too early, Mikoto.
Says he doesn't know.
I see... Let's go.
- Fuck this guy. - All this action made me hungry...
See you.
We have enough personnel.
- Keep the others out. - Roger that.
They're on the floor above!
It's those Blues!
SCEPTER 4 has entered the building.
What should we do, Mikoto?
Burn them.
Oh yeah!
Let's do it, guys!
- Yeah! - Yeah!
No blood! No Bone! No Ash!
The Third King, Mikoto Suoh is activating his sanctum.
Weismann level at 75, 80...
Vertical over!
Here it comes... The Sword of Damocles.
It's huge!
Very well...
We will advance with swords in hand!
For our cause is pure!
Men! Draw your swords!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
- Akiyama, ready! - Benzai, ready!
- Kamo, ready! - Domyoji, ready!
- Enomoto, ready! - Fuse, ready!
- Goto, ready! - Hidaka, ready!
Munakata, ready!
Arriving now at track two,
the 8:05 bound for Ashinaka High School campus.
Please stand clear of the doors.
I'm sure you are all busy preparing for the upcoming school festival.
But please refrain from getting carried away with the festivities,
and remember to uphold the tradition
and honor of this school.
Die!
Listen, I forgot to bring my lunch today.
Don't lie!
- Can I have some of yours? - No!
- About Shiro... - I don't think so.
Not today!
Shiro...?
- Don't you ever get tired of asking? - You mean Yashiro Isana?
Does he have any friends?
What?
No...
The guy seems pretty popular to me.
- Whoops! - A joker to be exact.
- But when you think about it... - Here you go.
- He's not really - Thanks!
- close with anyone... - Thank you!
Oh yeah, and he's not eating enough veggies.
Veggies?
- His diet is leaning towards - Here!
too much meat consumption,
because he only goes after the main dishes.
So, today...
I'm going to fix that by giving him this nutritionally balanced
combination of nimono, salad, and cooked veggies!
Huh?
Oh no, he's leaving!
He's gone.
Where'd he go?!
- Want some? - Yes, please!
You want mine too?
Gimme!
- Here you go. - I have some for you too!
I'm all yours!
Hey, there's some over here too!
- Thanks! - Here!
Take it.
- Let's go! - Right!
You again?
That scared me!
Oh, sorry!
You're too kind.
- Show some respect! - Tsk!
He sure runs away fast!
Where'd you go?!
You're too kind.
Hmm... it's love...spinning its wheels...
No, it's not that.
Huh?
I feel like if I take my eyes off of him, he'll just fade away...
Oh, hi.
Japan is at peace.
What a wonderful country!
This country will come to an end, Weismann!
Did you just say something?
Yes, you are like a rose to me...
Say your lines like you're singing it!
And vice versa!
Huh?
What about class?
We have the afternoon to prep for the school festival.
Give us a hand.
Sorry!
Can someone run an errand for the Student Council?
We need somebody who's free!
Let's see... Okay!
Shiro, I'm sending you the list.
Here.
Huh?
That's funny...?
You don't have your PDA?
Okay, I'll write it down.
But you need to find your PDA first,
or you can't leave the school...
No problem.
Can we stop somewhere on the way home?
Sure. Where are we going?
That new place from yesterday.
- Oh, okay then. - No problem.
Let's see...
Go to Kagitama Store over in Shizume Town
to pick up the fireworks for the event.
Hand them the voucher and money.
Then head back to the Ashinaka High School Student Council...
and give them the receipt.
Nice weather...
Oh, right... Receipt, receipt...
Get the receipt and be back by six.
The place is...
Turn right by the huge TV...
The fire lights, showing the shadow of a foreign king...
Come again!
Thanks.
Huh?
Excuse me!
Get back here!
Sorry!
Out of the way!
Damn. Who was that guy?!
Kuroh Yatogami, the "Black Dog."
We've got trouble on our hands.
Oh well. Guess we'll have to go with Plan B.
You brought us near the station.
Thank you. You've been a big help.
See you.
I am a vassal of the former Seventh King, Ichigen Miwa...
Kuroh Yatogami.
"Vassal of the Seventh King, Ichigen Miwa"...?
Oh, is that your name?
How do you do? My name's Isana.
Yashiro Isana...
In compliance with my late master's dying wish,
I will slay the evil king!
King...what?!
Huh?
That's odd...
It won't turn off.
Huh? What is that?!
Hey, it's a nice night out.
I came out here to take pictures of the nighttime view,
but what are you doing out here?
I'm Tatara Totsuka. What's your name?
I am the Seventh King, the colorless king!
I'm waiting for someone here.
A nice night, you say?
Indeed it is.
Block 2 has been jacked!
- What about your side? - Block 4 has also been jacked!
Someone's hijacked the city's urban network.
Track down the source!
That's what we're doing...
It's so unlike you to pull off such a cheap move.
That's definitely you, right?
Uh... Yeah, looks like it...
Hello! I'm Yashiro Isana, the protagonist of the show
who's in the middle of getting himself killed.
By the way, what do you think of someone
who points a sword towards a person they've just met?
I'd say they're kind of rude and lack common sense, don't you agree?
Ow, ow, ow! Hey! Why are you stabbing me?!
Cut it out, I'm bleeding!
N-Next time on  K , #02 "Kitten."
Um... Anyone have a bandage?