Die!
COOK
KEEP WARM
Fold the omelet quickly while the egg is still half-cooked.
The outside should be a bright, golden yellow.
Yashiro Isana.
Per your request, I have prepared lunch for you.
Do not, however, seal the box until the contents have cooled.
I've cooked the omelets to be sweet and fluffy,
but let me know if you prefer Dashi egg-rolls instead!
Ohh!
You! What are you doing?!
Die!
Wait!
That's not trash!
Die!
Huh? You can't be serious! Me too?!
Show some respect.
You hillbilly samurai!
Stop bullying...
- Shiro! - Know your place!
- This is no time for games! - Take that, and that,
- What are your plans? - and that!
- Plans? Go to school, of course. - You will pay for this!
- I have to turn in my assignment... - Shiro isn't trash!
- for classical literature class. - Have mercy!
- You... - Die!
- Have you forgotten what you said? - You're too kind!
I have failed...
Huh?!
Do you have any intention of proving your innocence?!
Shiro, I'm glad you got to see your friend.
Yeah, I guess.
And who might you be?
I am a vassal of the former Seventh King, Ichigen Miwa,
Kuroh Yatogami.
What he's trying to say is... he's a transfer student...sort of.
Please do not mind me.
I see...
Thank you for helping me the other day.
I didn't know you were a transfer student.
I'm Kukuri Yukizome.
Kukuri Yukizome...
Just call me Kukuri.
So your name's Kuroh?
Kuro and Shiro— "black" and "white," like the game Othello.
WHAT IS MY ALIBI? If there's anything you need help with, feel free to ask.
Thank you.
Stop!
I admire your courage.
And, who might you be?
She's a transfer student...sort of.
Shiro brought a homemade lunch...
Made by my wife, with love.
That's not funny. Now stick out that tongue.
Any leftovers?
Want some?
Nothing but veggies...
Hey, where'd you get that?
It doesn't look like our school issued PDA.
It's my wife's.
Hope you've said goodbye to your tongue.
Did you find out anything?
No, can't tell anything from this blurry image.
What're you looking at?
Huh?
EARLIER IN THE DAY
Hey, Shiro!
I found the nastiest video yesterday.
You're really into that stuff, aren't you, Mishina?
I'm not that interested in erotic videos.
Yeah, you are!
But this one was different!
Wait, you haven't told Miss Yukizome about
that porn pic I showed you the other day, have you?
No.
Good.
Anyway, here!
Check this one out.
He looks exactly like you, Shiro!
You're right.
If you committed a crime, turn yourself in, okay?
Mishina, that video of the guy who looks just like me has me worried.
Could you forward it to me?
It's an uncanny video I got from Mishina.
Huh? From Mishina...?!
Oh, come to think of it...
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Why don't you help us out instead of just slacking off?
I'm not slacking off, ma'am.
According to this video,
the crime occurred on December 7th at 23:45.
The location is the rooftop of the Hirasaka Building
in the West Precinct.
So Mr. Totsuka's dead...
Lieutenant Awashima!
Do we know his current location?
Yes. One moment.
Ashinaka High School?
So he's on the school island...
The video that was aired across the city,
was dated December 7th, 23:45 at night.
Given the distance between my school and the crime scene,
there is no way I could have made it back in one hour.
Which means...
That's right.
If I can prove I was on campus on the 7th at around 23:45,
I would have an alibi...
But you live alone.
Claiming you were asleep by yourself isn't an alibi.
And just to be clear,
I'm not accepting anything this one says as an alibi!
Stupid Kurosuke!
Shiro and I have been together from the moment we met!
My Shiro is a good Shiro.
Quiet!
I said I don't trust you.
If I find out you had a hand in his crimes, you'll pay dearly.
Prepare yourself for that.
Now, now... Things will be all right...
That was the day we had permission to work on the school festival at night.
It's coming back to me now...
All kinds of incidents happened that day.
Incidents?
Yeah.
So I'm positive somebody can prove that I was there.
C'mon! How long does it take you to change?!
Hey, you look good!
Seriously Shiro,
you make a great Ebisu, even though you're not fat.
That's pretty rare, you know.
And you, miss, look beautiful.
I am beautiful!
Kukuri, do you have a second?
It's about December 7th...
Here it comes...
Here.
He's a student at the school on the island?
Of all the difficult places...
What'll we do?
How the fuck should I know?!
Yata?
That idiot...
Miss Kukuri Yukizome!
The minute I saw you, it was love at first sight!
Please be my girl!
I'm...
I'm sorry!
My heart is broken!
And that's what happened.
Why're you bringing that up again?
The feeling of love
A shower of fireworks It bursts then fizzles
Creepy!
But boy, that was quite a show.
It happened just before midnight, right?
Around 23:45 to be exact?
Yeah, it was... But why is that so important?
I was there watching it, remember?
I don't know.
Maybe you were, but I'm not really sure.
Hey, come on...
That was the last thing on my mind!
Is that guy planning to blow up all the school festival fireworks?!
Drag him out of there, quick!
Here comes the student council!
Remove the door. We're going in!
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM During that whole incident,
I was also there.
Do you recall?
Nope.
I was too busy dragging down that idiot from up there.
Yes, things were going really out of control.
If you hadn't acted so swiftly,
who knows what might've happened?
Would you like to check the news article from that day?
LOVELORN FIREWORKS LIGHT UP THE NIGHT! - BY THE DAILY ASHINKA
LOVELORN FIREWORKS LIGHT UP THE NIGHT! - BY THE DAILY ASHINKA I'm not in the photo.
If you want a photo of yourself during the commotion,
why not ask someone at the school newspaper?
They were taking lots of photos that day.
That's right...
After that, the class president dealt
with one issue after another effectively.
There should be photos of all of that.
By the way...
I realize we're getting ready for the school festival,
but you can't go around school dressed so outrageously.
Especially you. Sword props like that are prohibited.
This is not a prop!
- Stop laughing! - Thank you for your time.
Easy there!
Awesome.
You idiot!
Oh no!
Somebody bring a fire extinguisher!
Stop that horse!
This has impact!
You! Go around that way!
Don't miss any sweet shots!
Right.
I'm not in here...
I'm positive I was around here someplace.
Are you sure?
- We have a ton of photos from that day, - Show some respect.
- so if you were there, you should... - I'm in heaven...
- be able to find yourself. - Show some respect.
But I'm not in here...
So you don't have an alibi, after all!
What's this about an alibi?
Was there an incident?
I smell a scoop.
No, it's nothing like that.
- You're too kind... - You're too kind...
- You're too kind... - You're too kind!
- This is a problem. - You hillbilly samurai!
- Easy there. - I was sure there'd be a photo.
You guys!
We're all super busy! Help us out!
Thank you.
Where does this go?
- Could you take that... - Die! - Have mercy!
- to the teachers' office? - Die! - Have mercy!
End of the line!
I have to bring this to the student council room.
Understood.
Oh, that's right.
The teachers' office.
Thank you. Leave it there, please.
Sir, I have a small favor.
You want to see a log of the students
who passed through the main gate?
Yes...
All right. But what do you need it for?
It's nothing that important...
Just that I might be killed.
Oh, I see.
What day are you looking for?
December 7th.
Let's have a look... The seventh...
Arisawa...Ariyoshi...Iida... Ikuno...and Inoue.
You see? There's no Yahiro Isana.
Shiro Shiro! I am hungry.
- This clears me of suspicion, right? - I am... I am...
I am...
Hungry!
Sorry...
There's nothing to worry about anymore,
so let's enjoy a snack.
Yahoo! A snack! A snack!
Speaking of snacks,
Kukuri said she had some delicious rice crackers!
And her friend said
she'll buy me some tasty Daifuku mochi!
Daifuku, Daifuku!
Oh, now I'm thirsty...
Shiro, can you buy me a drink?
Like I told you...
Everyone who enters or leaves this island
is scanned and checked at the automatic gate.
If I'm not on this list,
it means I was on this island the whole time,
and couldn't have been at the scene of the crime.
Get it?
I want juice.
Oops, not enough small change.
Forgot your PDA again?
It's a rule— you have to keep it on you.
Isn't it inconvenient without it?
Kukuri, are you saying he does not carry a PDA with him?
He always forgets, no matter how many times I tell him.
Without his PDA, he could not get past the gate, correct?
This guy just sneaks out.
Kukuri, something is about to happen that will make you nauseous.
Leave us.
W-Wait a minute!
I'll get serious! I'll find real proof!
I've heard enough.
It's become quite clear that you are insincere.
Step aside.
Or are you working for him, after all?
Is it your wish to be slain with your master?
I am Neko!
I am Shiro's cat!
I'm not letting you take him, Kurosuke!
Shiro is a warm person and
I'm going to have delicious meals and snacks with him!
Easy, Neko...
You're making things more complicated.
Shiro... Shiro...
I'm...sorry, Kuro.
I'll get more serious from now on.
A lot more happened that day!
There was the sprinkler that broke, the toilet that overflowed,
and the school gym storeroom ceiling that caved in, just to name a few!
I had to be there, somewhere!
Hold on.
If it's the school gym storeroom, then I did see you, Shiro.
That day, after I ran away from the incident Mishima caused,
Shiro and I found this hole together.
Yeah, that's right.
Do you remember around what time that was?
That would be 12:30.
That's within an hour of the crime!
It would have been impossible
to return here from the crime scene by then.
That means...I have an alibi!
What? What are you talking about?
I owe you my life... That's what.
Stop dawdling!
Remember, we don't have much time until the school festival!
Yes, sorry!
It's incredible.
- Ever since Kuro got serious... - Less talking, more action!
about helping us, we're getting so much done.
Really! The transfer student's working so hard
while that guy disappears again.
A bigger concern is...
Are these people really transfers?
Boy, I'm beat!
Having someone try to kill you every day is exhausting.
Oops, I left my uniform in the classroom.
Well, that's okay...
Hey, it's a nice night out.
I came out here to take pictures of the night view,
but what are you doing out here?
I'm Tatara Tosuka. What's your name?
I am the Seventh King, the Colorless King!
I'm waiting for someone here.
A nice night, you say?
Indeed, it is.
Shiro!
W-What's the matter?
Oh yeah, your snack.
Kukuri gave me super-spicy rice crackers,
and asked me to call you.
After I do that, she promised me ultra-spicy rice crackers!
Okay, I'll be right there.
Shiro?
Do you have a tummy ache?
It's nothing.
No, it can't be...
You're too kind.
So this is where that piece of shit is...
Just you wait, I'll tear you apart...
Huh?
I had an early shift, and now, I'm doing overtime?
Can't we just let HOMRA take care of Tatara Totsuka's murderer?
Why do we have to go through all the trouble?
Yeah, yeah, the next preview, right?
I'm doing it now.
Next time... Oh?
So he's coming, huh?
Finally...
Next time, on K, #05 "Knife."
I should be the object of your hate, not him!