I'm sure you are all busy preparing for the upcoming school festival.
But please refrain from getting carried away with the festivities,
and remember to uphold the tradition and honor of this school.
Your families will be joining us on festival day.
Show them the results of all the hard work
- Are these all of the costumes? -  you put into this past few weeks...
Okay, everyone check your own costumes.
Let me know if you're having any trouble with the size.
How are the decorations coming along?
We're not quite done...
Okay, I'll help you.
Who else is free right now?
Rice crackers...
- What is it, Kuro? - Rice crackers...
- Your sleeve is torn right near the elbow. - Rice crackers...
Oh, you're right.
- I must've caught it on something. - Rice crackers!
- When can I have my rice crackers?! - Let me...
fix that for you.
Hold still.
Rice crackers...
My rice crackers...
Rice crackers!
We'll be done in a minute.
That would be 12:30.
That's within an hour of the crime!
It would have been impossible to return here
from the crime scene by then.
Yashiro Isana!
That's enough dawdling!
Shiro got a scolding!
Kuro! Please keep your eyes on what you're doing!
Sorry...
What was I supposed to be doing, now?
Let's all have some rice crackers!
I said to get working!
Please, Kuro!
I know...
Shiro, if you don't have anything to do,
can I ask a favor?
Yes.
Yes, that's correct.
At Ashinaka High School.
The Yuishiki System has found someone there
who is a 91 percent match.
Yes, I'm positive.
I'd like to go there personally to be sure.
I understand. Goodbye.
We have authorization.
We will now head to the school on the island
to confirm the suspect's presence.
- Yes, ma'am! - Yes, ma'am!
Have a safe trip...
You're coming too, Fushimi.
Are you serious?
What will you do when you find him?
Take him into custody, of course.
And if he resists?
That's a stupid question.
So we use this to get in?
What a pain in the ass.
Let's go.
Right!
We're going for a walk!
Why do you keep using this exit?
I told you. I lost my PDA.
Oh, wait. Maybe I should just install my passcode into yours.
Request for a new one already!
Shiro! Hurry, hurry!
We have to order more fireworks
because you blew up all that we had.
I had no choice. You were trying to kill me.
Don't you realize how busy we are?
Sounds like you're starting to fit right in...
Die!
Show some respect...
All right. We're going in.
Okay.
We apologize for this rather sudden request,
but we need your cooperation.
I want to reiterate.
We will not cause your school any trouble.
Yes, but...
Given the current times,
releasing personal student information is, how should I put it...?
I need you to understand that if need be,
we are not above using legal means.
We can't have that!
No. We would like to handle things as amicably as possible, as well.
Therefore, we'd prefer that you cooperated willingly.
I...understand.
But to find a student whose name and class you don't even know
from among the entire student body is...
As a practical matter,
there's little we can realistically do right away...
Let me make myself clear...
This investigation has already been authorized.
If your school lacks the means to conduct an investigation,
we will do it for you.
You'd do it yourselves?
That's going too far!
I think you're misunderstanding. We are not trying...
to "persuade" you.
We are here to explain the situation
and to "order" you to act accordingly.
But that's...
As I said earlier, it is not our wish to turn this into a pubic issue.
However, I have no reservations about using the law...
...to take appropriate action.
Hey, know this guy?
Come back here!
Know where we can find this guy?
You know this guy, don't you?!
Yata, let's ask them next.
We're moving on.
Wait up, Yata!
You're too damn slow!
Geez!
It's all that stuff you eat while we're on the job...
That's why you're so fat!
What about you, Yata? Have you been eating?
I haven't seen you take any breaks at all ever since that day.
I'm fine.
STUDENT COUNCIL
Huh?
NOT A MATCH
Take a good look, you!
You shifted your eyes, didn't you?!
N-No! I didn't!
You know this guy, don't you?!
I don't! I have no idea!
Where is he, damn it?!
You can't run away!
Another dead end. Shit!
Yata, this isn't gonna work. This place is huge.
Shut up!
I don't want to waste another second,
to avenge Mr. Totsuka's death!
Hey... You two!
Come here a second.
We want to ask you something!
Uh, we don't...
Huh?
What's the matter?
I just said we want to ask some questions.
Ouch!
Idiot!
Don't scare girls like that, or I'll kill you.
Hey, sorry about!
Cut me some slack, Yata!
Shut up!
I keep telling you! Don't ever threaten the ladies!
But I didn't...
All this time, Yata, you've only been talking to guys.
We need to ask girls, too...
To find a guy, you ask guys!
Huh?
Still can't get yourself laid, huh?
You bastard...
Saruhiko!
Fancy meeting you here. How'd you find this place?
Oh, you had Anna's help.
But Mr. Kusanagi wouldn't send you here to ask questions.
My guess is you acted on your own again, huh, Misaki?
You never change.
Shut the fuck up!
Don't go calling me by my first name!
Or talk about my people like you know them.
You traitor!
Can you blame me?
In the end, I wasn't like you and the others.
Leaving was inevitable.
Damn right about that!
You're not like us!
Yata, you can't make a scene here...
So, Misaki, how'd you manage to sneak in here?
Huh? None of your business.
Security's tight here.
Where's your pass? Show it to me, Misaki.
It's none of your business!
And don't call me by my first name. Gives me the creeps.
Oh yeah, you hate being called by that name...
Mi...sa...ki...
You asked for it...
Yata!
Don't do this!
Remember what Mr. Kusanagi said!
Don't let Mr. Mikoto's capture be in vain!
What good would fighting that Monkey here do?!
Mr. Mikoto...eh?
That man seems to have lost his edge.
After all, he went to jail willingly.
Guess it means he's grown up.
You could learn from him, Mi...sa...ki.
Yata!
Monkey!
Die, you bastard!
Fushimi, ready for emergency battle.
Not as sharp as you used to be, Monkey.
No...
I've become stronger than before...
Much stronger.
Bullshit!
What's the matter, Monkey?!
Yata!
I just told you...
I've acquired even more power since leaving Mikoto Suoh's side.
This is the proof.
T-Two colors?!
Damn it!
Stay out of this, punk.
This is no place for a loser like you!
Monkey's...
right.
Keep out of this.
Yata...
Monkey, don't get cocky because of those half-assed powers.
Think you own the country now?
I'm not interested in anything as crass as the country.
What I'm interested in is...
blood and flesh...
That's enough!
That's enough, you two!
Put away your sword!
Fushimi!
What do you think you're doing out here in broad daylight?
Did you forget where we are right now?!
You are Misaki Yata of the militant faction
under the Red King, are you not?
You wield a skateboard and
serve as the vanguard of Team HOMRA
and go by the name of...Yatagarasu.
I know about you, too.
You're the Blue King's right-hand woman, Seri Awashima.
People call you... The Heartless Woman.
The only person who calls me that is the owner of a certain bar.
Huh?
Be that as it may, I cannot condone your presence here.
But unfortunately,
there's too much to lose if I make an issue of it here.
How about if the two of you postpone your match?
He started it.
Is that so? Perhaps I didn't make myself clear.
You  will  postpone your match. Comply.
Was that better?
I don't have a reason to obey you, Blues.
Yata!
Your king...
All he does is complain about how bad the food is,
finishes up, and then goes to sleep like a baby.
He's quite a piece of work.
Mr. Mikoto...
Let's go.
Is it okay to let them go?
We have no choice.
Fushimi.
Do you have something to tell me?
I'm very sorry.
So, how'd it go?
How'd what go?
Don't play dumb.
You were accessing the school's data, weren't you?
That should do it for now.
Let's go back, Yata.
Yata!
I heard you.
After one more person!
I want to ask just one more person!
Wait...Yata!
Ugh, what was it? I swear I heard it a minute ago.
Hey, you there!
Yes?
I-I'm looking for someone...
This guy...have you seen him?
Well? Is that boy a student here?
Well?
No.
I'm sorry.
NO MATCHES FOUND
The suspect is not a student at this school.
I don't know him.
Fuck! Another dead end!
Worst part, I had to run into that Monkey!
I can't afford to lose any more time in finding the bastard!
Those stupid, but fun times I spent with Mr. Mikoto,
the guys, and that person...
That bastard destroyed it all!
Next time on K, #06 "Karma."
Those days will never come back...