It's those Blues!
SCEPTER 4 has entered the building.
Munakata, ready!
I'll handle this.
In compliance with Protocol 120, I am taking you into custody.
Any objections?
Unfortunately, I have none.
Take good care of me.
Well, look who's here...
Suoh, let's get straight to the point.
Your Weismann level is pushing its limit.
If the Sword of Damocles should fall,
we'll have a repeat of the Kagutsu crater.
If you insist on drawing more power from the Dresden Slates,
I will have to kill you.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I'm telling you to renounce your throne.
You're just a stick in the mud, aren't you, Munakata?
If that's your answer,
I'll have to come up with a way to keep you locked up for life.
Actually, there is one way to keep me locked up here forever.
You could do it, Munakata.
The Blue King can keep an eye on me personally.
24 hours a day, inside this cell.
If I become violent, you can restrain me by force.
The thought of having to breathe the same air as you makes me ill.
And besides, I'm afraid I'm quite busy.
I can't spend all my time with you.
I'm sorry you feel that way, Munakata.
Yeah, me too, Suoh...
Restraining him with fire-retardant phenolic resin...
That sounds like a good idea.
But I don't know how effective it'd be against that man.
I do not know what the Red King, Mikoto Suoh, has in mind,
but this gives us a good opportunity.
If I may be so blunt,
short of killing him, we should try every available option.
For example, under proper medical supervision,
how about administering doses of muscle relaxant or tranquilizers?
That's quite a radical idea and a good one at that, Ms. Awashima.
Your blatant disregard for Suoh's human rights
makes me shudder.
All right. I'll consider it.
Did you learn anything about the weapon used
to murder Tatara Totsuka?
Apparently, it was one of many modified guns
that the mafia was dealing.
The man in charge of their smuggling operation has gone missing,
along with the truck.
Was there anything else on that truck?
A few volatile chemicals, explosives,
and enough weapons and ammo to open up a gun shop.
Those bastards...
Well, if the suspects have their hands on that much firepower...
Metro P.D. is taking this very seriously,
and is about to form an investigation unit.
I'm thinking of putting in a special request
for a release of information.
Shall I issue the order under Level: Prussian Blue?
No, make it the next level: Royal Blue.
I want to know of every incident
that has occurred in this city in the past two weeks,
as well as everything that may or will happen until this case is solved.
I want every set of eyes and ears you have on this.
Understood.
And those who can't handle it have no need for eyes and ears.
It is our duty to manage and make use of them.
You are an exceptional woman, Ms. Awashima.
How's it coming?
I'm just about done spicing up the video
HOMRA spammed across the net.
We have the algorithm to manage all the information.
Then, I leaked some gossip questioning the validity of the video.
So far, I've kept it confined to the level
of a well-conceived Internet prank.
How about you?
I'm checking the database for people with criminal records, but...
I'm not getting any hits.
I just hope the Greens don't catch on to this.
All right. I'll be right there.
Can you pass me the soy sauce?
Show your gratitude. For your meal is important.
Now chew and savor.
There you have it. Eat properly.
What was that?
I see.
They do work fast.
Nah, don't worry.
As long as the video still exists, it'll get us somewhere.
Okay, understood.
Yes, yes...
Thanks.
Although, if the Black Dog joined the other side,
this is going to be a real bitch.
Not to mention we're running out of time.
What did you just say?!
Shut up!
You fucking pussy!
Uu... I can't breathe.
M-My...bar!
Why don't you try and say it again, huh?
Dammit you guys!
Listen, you punks!
This bar was specially imported from a pub in England.
It cost me a fortune!
The scent of ale, cigarettes,
- and the chatter of drunken patrons... - Mr. Kusanagi...
- are soaked into this fine piece of history. - You're going to crush my skull!
- With every polishing, - Please, let go!
- the luster of the rosewood... - Ow! Oww!
So...
Care to tell me how this fight all started, boys?
Well, this idiot badmouthed Mr. Mikoto!
No, I didn't!
What about Mikoto?
He said Mr. Mikoto crossed over to the Blue!
Give him hell, too, Mr. Kusanagi!
No! That's not true!
- I was just wondering why... - Don't make excuses!
the King let himself be captured without a fight.
- H-Hey! Don't kick me! - Bastard! That's the same thing!
- It's completely different! - Yeah? Say it again, and I'll...
Want me to tell you?
- Huh? - Huh?
Why Mikoto purposely allowed himself to be captured?
Uh...Yes.
If you apologize to my bar with respect, I'll tell you.
O-Okay.
- We are sorry. - We are sorry.
Think about it.
They're trying to confine a guy
who's a natural disaster waiting to happen.
Worst-case scenario,
the Blue King will have to stay with him at all times.
What would happen then?
It makes it easier for us to make moves, right?
Mikoto let himself be captured so we could roam free.
You see, I told you!
Let's get out there and search for that piece of shit, and the Black Dog!
Huh?
We won't let Mr. Mikoto down!
R-Right.
See you, Mr. Kusanagi!
I'm counting on you, Yata!
You got it!
Liar.
C'mon, cut me some slack.
It's sort of true.
By the way,
I wanted to ask you, while I have the chance...
Who were those fire guys who came chasing after me?
Their fellow clansman was killed.
Now, they're out for revenge.
Clansman?
Like a motorcycle gang or the mafia?
A clan is a group of people who serves under their king.
Clansmen are the members of that group.
Mikoto Suoh, the Red King, is the king of the third clan.
Of all the kings, he is the most violent-tempered.
So you're saying he's the boss of a group of people with psychic powers?
And that there are other groups like his?
I'm being mistaken
for the guy who murdered one of their members, huh?
Not mistaken for... you  are  the murderer.
After we're done eating, I'm killing you.
What?!
More!
Then I'll have more, too!
Well, this is going to be the last bowl of white rice you'll ever eat.
Hey, wait a minute!
Found them!
Over here, too!
This is the missing gun dealer's spot, all right!
How the hell does Mr. Kusanagi get a hold
of this kind of information, anyway?
Rumor has it that
this dealer isn't the only guy who mysteriously disappeared.
Looks like Mr. Kusanagi made the connection
between them and Totsuka's murder.
I'm gonna need to hear more about what you just said, scumbag.
What the hell?!
Y-You're...!
Who is this guy?
He's Fushimi!
That guy who betrayed us?!
Guess he's not here...
I found the missing gun dealer's warehouse.
Tell Lieutenant Awashima and clean up this mess.
Show some respect.
You're too kind.
Moving onward.
I understand now why those people are after me.
But why do you want to kill me?
It's not like you're one of them.
It's because I am the vassal
of the previous Seventh King, the Colorless King.
Colorless?
It means one who is not beholden to a color.
My late master ordered me to evaluate
the man who would be the next King,
and to kill him without hesitation if he is evil.
Master Ichigen Miwa, the previous King,
possessed the ability to predict the future.
The ability to see the future...
The Colorless King...
For starters, what is this "King" you keep talking about?
One endowed with great power
that embodies the natural laws of this world.
The power of the king is what runs this country.
Ordinary human beings would not know of this, however.
I thought the Prime Minister was the most powerful man in this country.
Yes, yes. I will see to it. Yes.
Yes, as you wish. Goodbye.
Mr. Prime Minister.
Here is the official document to issue Level: Royal Blue.
I already received a call from His Excellency regarding that matter.
Both Captain Munakata and His Excellency
value regulation above all else.
SCEPTER 4 will now institute the Yuishiki System.
For two weeks, the people will be disenfranchised of their rights.
I hope you understand.
We don't have the right of refusal.
You're well aware of that.
Just following regulations, sir.
Good grief...
Even though we have no choice,
it's not easy going along with the King's whimsical decisions.
RECHARGING - ONE MOMENT - Today, this country's government... -  One moment please.
RECHARGING - ONE MOMENT - and economy cannot function... -  One moment please.
without the power of one man.
It was because of him that Japan was able to transform
from a once-defeated nation, preyed upon by its neighbors,
into the world's greatest economic and technological power.
Who is he?
He is known as the Golden King.
His influence extends to all aspects of society.
For example...
Both of these were made by companies
controlled by the Golden King.
The boss of those fire guys...
You called him the Red King, didn't you?
So there's a Red and Gold King?
There are seven kings.
Seven?
Each clan is completely different
depending on the King who rules them.
If I were to describe the Red Clan in a word, it would be...
Violence.
What the hell...
I rushed over because I heard
there was trouble with the guy who killed Totsuka...
These were the guys you meant?
Damn you, punk!
What do you think you're doing?!
Yata...
Help me out here. These guys won't go away!
They want me to tell them about you!
Get lost.
You heard me, get lost.
Or else you're going to be in a lot more pain.
Fuck you!
So you guys want to know about us?
Then, I'll tell you.
I'm HOMRA. We are HOMRA.
Mr. Mikoto taught us that.
This represents our pride...
Hey, jerk offs.
I'm giving you a good story here...
Pay attention!
What should we do to them, Yata?
As much as we can without killing them.
They're a clan with bonds that run thicker than blood.
Killing one of their members was an awfully stupid thing to do,
King-to-be.
Look! I keep telling you it was someone who looks like me!
I'm not the "King" you talk about, and I've never killed anyone!
- See those men?! - Yes...
- They trashed my place! - Oh, is that so?
Are you listening to me?!
- Business is shot for the night! - Yes, over at the shopping district.
- Why don't you two come to my shop?! - There was an assault.
- I'll open just for you. - Please send back up.
No, that's all right.
- Looks like I just missed them... - Oh, come on..
Stop by again, okay?
Why...?
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for the meow.
Okay, time to kill you.
Wait, wait! This isn't right!
Let's think about this rationally.
Your reason for wanting to kill me
is because I am the evil Colorless King, correct?
Based on what?
That video.
That could've easily been faked!
Don't you think it's strange?
Why would I purposely identify myself as the Colorless King?
Because you're evil and want to show it.
If so!
I messed with that group of dangerous people.
By now, wouldn't I have run away to someplace a lot safer.
Wouldn't I?
I keep telling you,
I'm just an ordinary high school student!
Then, who is that?
Isn't she one of your Clansmen?
Huh? No, she's uh....
Who exactly are you?
Or...what are you?
I am Neko.
Could she be a Strain?
Then is it purely coincidence that she's here?
No, that can't be...
Strain?
There are those who possess special powers
without receiving them from a king.
Is that what you are?
I don't quite understand it, but I am Shiro's cat...
and Shiro is mine!
- Thanks, I guess... - I am Shiro's cat, and Shiro is mine!
Listen, Kuroh Yatogami...
I'm being falsely accused here!
I'm going to prove my innocence to you!
And I'll clear up the misunderstanding with those scary people.
I swear...I haven't killed anyone!
Didn't your late master tell you to kill me
after you made a precise evaluation?
Then determine with your own eyes!
Whether I am good...or evil!
Push a button.
Huh?
Just do it.
Okay...then...
Do not judge the cold
Without first knowing the warmth Of the shining sun
What is that?
It means don't jump to judgment.
Looks like you just got a new lease on life, Yashiro Isana.
Just Shiro is fine.
Mind if I call you Kuro?
Yashiro Isana...
As you wish, from this moment on,
I will determine what kind of person you are.
If I find that you are evil, I will slay you without hesitation.
Do we understand each other?
Thank you, Kuro.
That's good enough for now.
Thank Master Ichigen for admonishing me.
What is that voice recorder?
You mean this?!
This contains the recorded words of my late Master Ichigen.
The words of Master Ichigen, who was also an avant-garde poet,
were so filled with deep meaning and beauty
that simply engraving them into my soul was not enough,
so I recorded them at every opportunity.
To this day, whenever I am unsure,
Walk casually
Along the path you have chosen The path to your dreams
There you have it.
Creepy!
Hey there!
It's me! That's right, Neko!
I'm feeling great!
But these clothes...are killing me!
Things would be much better if there were no clothes at all!
Hey, that's it!
Next week, I'll use my powers to make those two completely naked!
Next time on K, #04 "Knock-on effect."
Don't worry!
They'll have their clothes on for the DVD release!