That's definitely you...
Right?
Yashiro Isana!
By order of the former Seventh King, Ichigen Miwa...
I shall have your...
Just a minute!
...life!
A-Are you really going to kill me?!
Do you intend to resist?
I didn't do it! I'm innocent!
Did this Miwa person order you to kill an innocent man?!
Innocent?
Okay, so...I might not look innocent at the moment...
But you know what they say...
Don't judge a book by its cover. It's what's inside that counts.
It's not a person's appearance, or even what's inside.
My policy is to judge a man by his actions.
I'm telling you, that's not me!
You have the wrong guy!
No matter how you look at it, that's you!
Stop trying to deny it!
Okay, so let's assume for a moment that I really did kill someone.
Why are you trying to kill me?
If you're accusing me of murder,
then shouldn't you just hand me over to the police,
and let a prosecutor and judge determine my guilt?
Isn't that how things should work in this law-abiding country?
I don't serve this country.
I serve only Master Ichigen Miwa.
I give up. Guess there's no point in arguing.
Go ahead and do what you want with me.
You've finally accepted your fate—
But before you do, would you grant me one final request?
Speak.
Mind putting me down first, though?
Don't worry, I won't run.
It'd be useless, anyway.
You'd catch me before I have a chance.
Right?
Cool. Thank you very much.
I want to write a farewell letter...
to my younger sister.
Your sister?
Yes, we're very close.
I know I can't prove to you that I'm innocent.
But I don't want my sister to believe...
that I was killed for committing murder.
She was born with a serious illness
and has lived her whole life in the hospital.
She's never had any friends,
so I'm the only person she can talk to.
If I'm killed, my sister will be left all alone.
What is your sister's name?
Huh?
Uh, it's...
Marilyn...
Uh... Mari. Her name is Mari!
Mari Isana. That's a nice name.
Thank you.
It's done.
I have a favor to ask.
Can you give this to her for me?
Please! There's no one else I can ask.
Once I'm gone, she'll have no family to turn to.
She'll be all alone.
What is this?!
I LIED.
I managed to get out of that one.
Next time, though, he'll kill me on the spot.
Did you put up the bounty notices?
I'm sending them out right...now!
NOTICE FROM HOMRA
WE ARE LOOKING FOR THE YOUNG MALE WHO SHOT OUR MEMBER ON THE ROOFTOP OF THE HIRASAKA BUILDNG ON THE NIGHT OF DECEMBER 7TH AROUND 23:45PM.
ANYONE WHO CAN PROVIDE INFORMATION LEADING TO THE SUSPECT'S CAPTURE WILL BE GIVEN A REWARD OF TEN MILLION YEN. What?! Are you serious?!
- That's insane! - Ten million?!
Hello, you've reached HOMRA.
Do you have information regarding the suspect?
Yes, that's correct. Ten million yen.
No, we're not joking.
Mind giving us a little credit?
Any luck, Anna?
Around this area.
Yatagarasu here.
All right. I'm on my way!
I just went into an alley that's not even on the map.
Stop laughing, moron.
Kamamoto here.
I have my hands full at the moment.
Give me a few minutes...
Hey, can I get a side of fried rice?
You moron! This is no time for lunch!
Hey, what did you just say about HOMRA?
Is someone running their mouth about HOMRA?
Mark the location. I'll head right over!
Try to focus on finding the boy.
Oh, and keep your hands off of the Black Dog.
You guys are no match for him.
Kusanagi out.
Mr. Kusanagi, just a minute!
Let's hope those boys don't screw this up.
Hey, you think that bounty's for real?
Are you serious?
What would you do with ten million yen?!
It's probably just another stupid prank by those HOMRA kids.
Hey, careful. You don't want to mess with those guys.
Where are you, Yashiro Isana?!
Come out!
Hey, Black Dog!
Where the hell is he?
What are you talking about, Red Clansman?
I'm asking where you're hiding that bastard!
If you know what's good for you, answer me!
I don't have time for you.
Move out of the way.
Hey!
Yatogami!
It looks like we can get out from up here.
Get up here, quick!
You!
It's him!
I'm sure you can take out that guy in an instant.
Just finish him off and come up here.
Don't underestimate me!
Once I'm done with you, I'll tie that idiot down.
If you intend to fight me, don't expect any mercy.
Fuck you!
Are you okay?!
Yata!
He's gone?!
Yashiro Isana...
Show some respect!
Oh sorry.
You're too kind.
Not at all.
I'm beat...
Who were those people, anyway?
And that video...
It seemed so real, like it was actually me.
I get the feeling this is gonna be a hassle.
I know. Especially when life was so good up until now.
Wh-Who are you?!
I am Neko!
- Show some respect! - Show some respect!
- Die! Die - Show some respect!
- You're too kind! - Die! Die
You're too kind!
School hours are now over.
I repeat, school hours are now over.
Students not preparing for the school festival
are asked to leave the school grounds immediately.
We're finally done for the day.
What's up with him?
He's kind of hot.
You really think so?
I'll just have to force my way through.
Excuse me... Can I help you with something?
What's wrong?
Friend of yours?
No, but he seemed like he needed some help.
I'm looking for a Yashiro Isana.
Do you know him?
Isana?
Oh, you mean Shiro?
Sure, he's my classmate.
Where is he?
Well, he went out to run some errands for me.
But he should be back by now.
If you'd like, I could show you to the student dormitory.
There we go!
Follow me. I'll take you to the boys' dorm.
Thank you. I am grateful for your cooperation.
You're being so dramatic! I'm just doing what's right.
Not many can do the "right thing" when it counts.
That is what my master used to say.
I will not forget what you have done to help me.
You're a funny guy.
So, how do you and Shiro know each other?
I have something that I must hand over to him.
Like something he dropped?
His death warrant.
Did you say...wallet?
No.
H-Here, put this on!
I don't want to!
A girl shouldn't run around naked.
Clothes are too restricting. I hate them!
Meow.
You want to play tag? Sure!
Sounds like fun!
Hey, Shiro!
I brought your friend to see you.
Friend?
How's your younger sister doing, Yashiro Isana?
Huh?
Shiro, you have a sister?
I appreciate your showing me here.
My pleasure!
I guess he's just as forgetful as Shiro.
No!
What the—?! How indecent!
Indecent! So indecent!
Here! Put this on, now!
This way, Shiro.
Huh? What?
Whoa! The hallway went back to normal!
Did she do that?!
Never mind. She needs to put on some clothes!
You're not getting away!
An illusion?!
Does she work for him?
What was that?
Are you okay?
Yes...
It felt like I bumped into something.
Meow.
Not again!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Give it up, Yashiro Isana!
The game's over.
Meow, meow, meow!
This wall's probably an illusion, as well!
Just give it up, Yashiro Isana!
- Stop it! Don't chase after Shiro! - I don't want to give up, okay?!
- How indecent! - Come on, put this on!
- Anyone who bullies Shiro gets this! - Hey, don't!
- Meat! - Don't do that!
This is an illusion... An illusion!
Huh? Hey, what did you just do to my face?!
You...
finally put it on...
Evil...King... Yashiro Isana...
MEAT STUPID By the order of my late master,
I shall...
Shiro, I'm hungry.
What do you say...
we set aside this matter for some breakfast?
What?!
Thank you for agreeing.
I've cooked rice before,
but I've never made anything to go with it.
Hurry, Shiro.
When is breakfast?
I'm hungry.
Which one goes in first? Dashi or Miso?
No! No green onions. I hate green onions.
What? But we have to put in green onions.
No yellow onions either!
I won't put that one in, so don't worry.
- And no myoga! And no ginger! - Not even that?! Ginger?
And no cilantro!
YOU FORGOT THIS! FROM KUKURI Oh, but I'm fine with garlic chives.
That, you're okay with?!
Oh, oh, I want mine spicy!
- Thank you again. - Let's put lots of hot pepper!
- We're not going to put that in. - Yes, we are! I want my mouth to be on fire!
We're not doing that.
Scrape the whites against the bottom of the bowl,
tearing, tearing the yolk...
Start from the skin...
Mince finely...
Eat while it's hot!
- Thank you for the food! - Thank you for the food!
Fresh eggs, soy sauce, and Dashi.
For kids, you can also add a pinch of sugar.
Now mix all of them gently.
Next, add oil to the frying pan, and then pour in the egg mixture.
Once the mixture starts to cook, push them to one side of the pan,
and then quickly roll it into its proper shape.
You roll it, got that?!
Next time on K, #03 "KITCHEN."
This is how you make a delicious Dashi egg roll.