They exist to protect.
I'm Tatara Totsuka. What's your name?
A nice night out, you say?
Indeed, it is.
Mikoto...
Don't go!
Shit...
I was there watching it, remember?
Maybe you were, but I'm not really sure.
Don't recall.
I'm not in here...
Here you go!
Three grilled fish lunches!
Hey.
Snap out of it.
Let me remind you. We are not done.
Huh? With what?
You're still under suspicion.
If you aren't the murderer,
then someone had to have framed you.
Oh, I see.
You have a point.
Yay!
We only stopped to eat here because you kept whining about being hungry.
Now try to behave a bit.
Sir, what are all these photos?
Oh...
They're photos of my regulars.
They've always been posted there.
I don't see mine up here.
Really? That's strange.
You're one of my most regular customers.
Shiro...?
And more soda on Thursday.
Thanks, 'bye.
I realize you're not open yet, but do you mind?
How can I refuse such a beautiful lady?
Besides, I hear you looked after my boys.
What'll you have?
Lieutenant Seri Awashima of SCEPTER 4...
a.k.a. the Heartless Woman.
Mind not telling your boys such strange things?
But Seri, your heart is ice cold.
Martini.
Oui, mademoiselle.
How would you like it today?
Let's see... Four parts gin to one part vermouth.
And...five scoops of red bean paste, please.
Oui, mademoiselle.
That's the one thing I'll never be able to love about you, Seri.
What is the Red King thinking?
Oh, right.
Sounds like our boss has been giving you guys a hard time.
You look very calm, considering your king is another king's prisoner.
What're you up to?
Hey, that's not a nice thing to say.
I don't understand how you can act so natural.
I'm sure you're aware, right?
Of what?
The Red King's Weismann level is reaching its limit.
You know what will happen
if he continues to exceed the limit, don't you?
You're referring to the Kagutsu Crater?
Now that's a disturbing thought.
That's how powerful a king is.
If they lose control,
there'll be changes to Japan's topography, just like last time.
Are you telling me you're okay with this city being blown off the map?
That's why he's with you...
At least you have someone who can stop him.
He probably wanted to get some sleep without worrying
about burning everything around him to the ground.
As far as I know, he's always been terrible
with stuff like self-control and patience.
He has no right to be a king.
He probably would have been happier
if he'd been born a lion in a wide savanna somewhere.
You're quite sentimental, aren't you?
Fine.
We'll just do our job.
Thanks.
Those belong to one of our guys.
He was a guy with a lot of expensive hobbies.
Thanks to him, my bar looks like a total mess.
By the way, Mikoto,
I understand that some middle school kid's been stalking you lately.
Yeah... You mean that annoying brat?
Hanging around you,
a guy who hates keeping friends, and...
who hates having people kiss up to him...
That kid's got balls.
HOMRA.
Uh, okay...
Thanks.
How should I tell you this...?
Tell me what?
It's about that kid who wants to work for you...
He was beaten up on the street and taken to the hospital.
Hey!
What brings you here, King?
King?
Who did this to you?
Look, kid...
If you hang around this guy, you'll end up like this again.
You might think you'll be safe near someone strong,
but it's the exact opposite.
Okay, I'll be careful from now on.
Kid, let me say this again...
I asked who did this to you!
Before I tell you, King...
I have a huge favor to ask. Will you hear me out?
My foot...
It itches like hell!
Could you scratch it for me?
Huh?!
Yes!
Ouch!
You're one reckless kid.
Don't blame me if he kills you.
Hey, don't sweat it... It'll all work out.
I'm going to become the king's vassal.
Huh?
That guy's going to become someone great.
He might become like a real king, don't you think?
You...
How am I supposed to read this?
Uh... I don't know.
What good is a note if you can't read it?!
Oh, wait, wait...
I'll try to remember what I was thinking when I wrote it.
Dammit, you...
Forget it.
It's faster if I just call and ask Kukuri.
What now?!
Why're you calling her?
What do you mean, why?
I asked her for her phone number just for this purpose.
You can go back and ask her directly!
C'mon, Shiro, let's go back!
Why do we need to go all the way back?!
What do you think we have phones for?!
I hate telephones!
Why?
Neko...?
What was that about?
Hello?
It's me, Isana. We're here to buy the fireworks, but...
Isana?
Do I know you?
What're you talking about? It's me, Yashiro Isana...
You know... Shiro.
Shiro?
I'm sorry, I don't know any Shiro.
I think you got the wrong number.
Hey, give me that.
What exactly happened?
Kukuri didn't recognize me.
Says she doesn't know of any Yashiro Isana.
Was that some sort of joke?
She didn't sound like she was joking.
Neko was acting strangely.
She might've done something to Kukuri.
Anyway, let's head back to the school.
Kuro...
Can I borrow your phone again?
What do you need it for?
I'm going to call my home...
Why?
I want somebody to tell me...
that I'm definitely Yashiro Isana.
Hello? This is Yashiro...
The number you have dialed is not in service at this time.
Please check the number and dial again...
Is everything okay?
What do you mean?
He looks stressed out...
Tonight's dinner is tom yam goong.
You're here?
Of course. This is where I take my afternoon nap.
Thank you for your hard work.
What work?
It was just a lame scuffle.
Mr. Kusanagi was complaining that
you really didn't have to deal with them in person.
Why'd I have to become king, anyway?
I knew all along.
You're different from other people.
I seem to attract every Tom, Dick, and Harry out there...
What kind of king is that?
You say that,
but they're all important to you, aren't they?
One day, I'll...
Hey, don't sweat it.
It'll all work out.
You've always been the carefree type.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You're a king.
Your powers are not meant for destruction.
They exist to protect.
I guarantee that.
What's tom yam goong?
You don't know?
It's a hot-sour soup.
It's bright red and looks terribly spicy,
but when you eat it, it has unexpectedly complex flavors.
It's red?
It sure is!
Anna, want to help me make it?
You're going to cook?
I'm into cooking right now...
When I tried calling my home,
I got a message saying the number wasn't in service.
Given that, what are the possibilities?
One: I called the wrong number for my house.
Two: Something happened at home that made them change their number.
Three: I'm lying.
Or four: There's something wrong with your memory.
I'm Yashiro Isana.
An ordinary guy from a pretty happy family
who's now living away from his parents to attend high school.
Where'd Neko go...?
Mr. Totsuka, you suck!
You did it all wrong.
You need to go bam! Then flip.
What?
I can't understand what you're saying, Yata.
Give me that.
Cut it out, you guys!
Play with your skateboard outside!
Okay, Mr. Totsuka, stomp on this end hard!
- That guy's... - Stomp it hard.
- a strange dude. - Like this?
- You got that right. - No, not sideways.
- He can't fight, - Back and forth!
- but he seems so comfortable in the midst... - Stomp hard on the back like this!
- of guys who do nothing but fight. - I got it. Don't worry.
- He's like a wild animal trainer. - Ready...go!
Hey, did you just laugh?
You really suck at this!
Look who's talking, Yata! You suck at Sevens!
What?!
What about you, Mr. Totsuka?
That's what happens when a guy who likes old-dude hobbies like bonsai
wants learn how to skateboard!
I enjoy trying lots of different things.
Which reminds me...
I bought an old-style movie camera.
Just take videos with your phone.
It just isn't the same.
I've been shooting a lot of clips. I'll show them to you sometime.
Your song.
Aren't you going to sing?
Anna's such a good kid.
Did you hear that?
There's a young lady here
whose heart's been captivated by one of my hobbies!
You're making too big a deal out of it...
At the crossroad where thousands of lives come and go every day.
That's where we met, you and I.
Those good old days
when we fooled around and laughed together...
Is this where you live?
It was supposed to be here.
Straight down the road after we left the station.
A small house with a yard...
It appears...
you are not who you think you are.
You're right.
I might not be Yashiro Isana at all.
In fact, Yashiro Isana may not have existed to begin with.
Yeah.
I had a feeling something wasn't right.
When I tried to remember details, things didn't turn out right.
Who are you?
A murderer?
I can't say with absolute certainty anymore, that I'm not one.
I can't believe myself anymore.
Do you want to slay me now?
Mr. Totsuka!
Hey! What happened?!
The...Colorless...King...
King?
Mr. Totsuka!
Was it another king that did this to you?!
That's enough, Yata! Don't make him speak!
You'll be all right, Mr. Totsuka.
We sent for a doctor.
We'll have you fixed up in no time.
Hey...
Don't...sweat it...
It'll all work out...
Sorry...
Mr. Totsuka?
Mr. Totsuka!
Don't fall asleep!
Don't do this to us! C'mon!
Sorry, Mikoto...
I have bad news.
Always being so irresponsible, and then dying on us like this...
Damn fool.
The final curtain ls at the very moment A person gives up
Such wonderful words.
Were you listening to what I was saying?
You mean about not being able to believe yourself?
Funny you should say that.
I don't believe you, either.
That was true well before you became unable to believe yourself.
I believe in only one thing.
My late master's words.
Master Ichigen said to be certain.
I have not yet given up making certain.
That is why I have no intention of allowing the final curtain to fall.
What about you, Shiro?
Don't give up, huh?
You're right.
Your Master Ichigen speaks the truth.
In that case, I will allow you to repeat his words.
Saying Master Ichigen's blessed words will cleanse your soul.
Creepy.
It's me, Neko!
Guess what, guess what?
Lots of Blue people stormed in and then, things went flash!
So I meowed and then,
the boob lady went boom, and kaboom!
And finally, the boss with glasses was all like...
Next time on K, #7 "Key."
But I'm sure it'll be okay, because I have Shiro!