Creepy.
Kuroh Yatogami and confederate!
What?
This is SCEPTER 4. In accordance with Article 2
of the Supernatural Regulation Exemption Act,
we are taking you into custody!
Huh? Uh...
I'm not sure what's going on, but uh... Sorry.
We refuse!
Permission to use our sabers...
Granted.
Men! Draw your swords!
- Akiyama, ready! - Benzai, ready!
- Kamo, ready! - Domyoji, ready!
- Enomoto, ready! - Fuse, ready!
- Goto, ready! - Hidaka, ready!
Awashima...
ready!
Huh?
What happened?
Oh, Neko!
What?! Where did all these civilians come from?
Wait... Something's not right!
Headquarters!
Headquarters, do you read?
Sensory interference.
Seal off the perimeter. Stay sharp!
I will handle this one!
- Man your posts! - Yes, sir!
Stand back.
Go ahead. Draw your sword.
This sword is not for killing the likes of you.
Then, be slain by "the likes of me"!
We seem to be lacking the winning edge.
Maybe it's time you went to work.
Let's see you dodge this!
What is that?
The Sword of...Damocles!
The Blue King... Reisi Munakata.
Well done...
Thanks to your efforts, I have a grasp of the situation.
Sir!
Guess I'd better get to work.
It seems Mr. Fushimi is growing impatient.
As I suspected, a third party,
an unknown Strain, was behind this.
By projecting her powers within a perimeter with herself at the center,
she can interfere and manipulate
the human senses and perceptions of those around her.
It is an all too dangerous power.
Uh... You think we should surrender?
I'll hold off that man.
The two of you fend for yourselves.
Huh?
Go!
But, Kuro...!
Seal the corridor!
Roger.
I'll send in the men on the outside.
I see... So you chose to sacrifice yourself.
The celebrated sword Kotowari...
It used to belong to the late Seventh King,
Ichigen Miwa, the Colorless King.
I suppose you could try and kill me with that.
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to draw your sword.
That's more like it...
What's this?
Such a disobedient child.
If you insist on being so stubborn, you leave me no choice.
Mr. Yatogami, what do you say we end this game?
I refuse...
Now then...
Let's get to the subject at hand.
This way!
Hurry, Shiro!
You showed magnificent self-sacrifice against me.
That young man...
Is he the master you serve now?
The Colorless King. The Seventh, and weakest king.
He is not a powerful presence alone,
but he is the wild card
who could tip the balance of power between the kings.
In other words,
he is the one person I need to be most wary of.
That young man is the new Colorless King
who will replace Ichigen Miwa...
Am I correct?
Answer me.
Master Ichigen told me to vet that man.
Oh? And what is your verdict?
I will not let anyone lay a hand on him until I make that decision.
I see...
That might have been his plan from the start.
Remaining neither good nor evil...
As long as he maintains that ambiguous position,
he can keep the "Black Dog," Kuroh Yatogami, as his bodyguard.
He could not ask for a more powerful pawn.
Using that young female Strain,
deceiving you and the people around him would be a simple matter.
All of us might be puppets in that young man's scheme.
Wouldn't you agree?
You have a point...
He's constantly laughing like a fool
and everything that comes out of his mouth is a lie.
That's the sort of fellow he is.
Is that man worth risking your life for?
Oh? Did you forget something?
You fool! Why'd you come backâ?!
Well, I guess I can't just leave my friends behind, can I?
I see.
So you came back to share your fate together.
That is a noble gesture.
But meaningless.
No... You see, it's not meaningless.
Oh?
You see... Kuroh, I'm sorry!
I've been lying to you all this time!
The truth is...
this is who I am.
Kuroh...
Can you hear me, Kuroh?
Captain!
The outer perimeter's been breached!
What?!
I should have known better...
I fell for it hook, line and sinker.
Fushimi, call in the local police.
Roger!
Hey! Are you okay?!
It's not serious...
I'll be fine in two minutes....
Say, Neko...
You were amazing back there.
Those people in blue were amazing too.
But the way you cleared the sky,
and then changed the scenery with lots of people showing up was just amazing...
And on top of that, you saved us.
I-I don't know what you're talking about...
What the Blue leader said about interfering with people's perceptions...
Was that what he was talking about?
Her powers aren't limited to visual and auditory hallucinations.
Her power to manipulate perception
can even play with a person's memory.
Huh? What do you mean?
This girl can create false memories in people,
and make people who've met for the first time
believe they're old friends.
You...
-  Mishina...  -  C'mon!
-  Here you go.  -  Thanks!
Here.
Hey, there's some over here too!
-  Thanks.  -  Here!
Oh...
I see now...
It's all finally coming together.
Okay, then.
Neko...
Fix this amnesia thing right now.
That way, we'll know for sure
if I'm that evil king you're chasing after.
If I find out that you are the evil king,
it means I will slay you on the spot.
Yeah, I suppose it does.
Your life is at stake.
Calm down and think it over.
I am calm!
I mean it.
At any rate, I'm okay with discussing this
after we've successfully escaped from here.
I'm tired of doing things that way.
"At any rate" this... or "for the time being" that.
If we keep putting this off like we have been,
we'll have nowhere to go next.
Unless we settle this right here, we can't move on.
How should I put this?
Regardless of who I was in the past or what I did,
I feel that the "me" of the present should take responsibility.
Such commendable words...
They don't match you.
Fine.
Thanks.
Okay, it's set then.
Do it, Neko.
Undo your spell completely.
No tricks.
You hillbilly samurai!
Hi, who are you?
Oh...I must've frightened you.
I'm sorry.
I thought I heard a loud noise just now...
What? Who?! Are you human?!
Uh...hi.
Are you all right?
Who are you? Where are you from?
Uh...I'm...
Yashiro...Isana.
Yashiro Isana?
That's right...Isana!
What were you doing here...?
Let me guess...
You were trying to avoid helping out with the school festival preparations.
Is that what I was doing?
Huh?
Whoa?! How'd that hole get there?!
Hole? I don't know...
Don't play dumb!
Huh? Is that all?
What about my memories before that?
This is where it started!
You were on the ground. You fell from the sky!
He fell to the ground?
I was the first one to find you!
I found you! That's why you're mine!
Shiro is Neko's Shiro!
You can't bring back memories of before you found me?
That's the part I want to know...
If you found out, wouldn't you disappear?
Wouldn't you no longer be Shiro?
Don't worry.
I'm your Shiro, right?
Okay...I'll try!
Bye!
Who...was that?
You got me. Thanks to you, my glasses are loose now.
Furthermore, we must assure prompt apprehension of the suspect.
Next time on K, #07 "KINDLING."
We stand firm in our resolve.