[screams]
[Announcer]
First and ten
on the New York 32.
Malone hands off to Riley
for a 1 yard gain.
[Commentator]
They can't establish
their running game
because Washington--
[man and woman
speak foreign language]
Mince and mash the garlic
into a paste.
My secret hideout.
Go, Oscar, go!
Reputed crime boss
Gaitano Cesare
once again avoided
prison
when a mistrial
was declared today
in his eight-week-long
RICO prosecution.
Allegedly responsible
for over 200 murders,
Cesare has yet
to spend one day
behind bars.
Mr. Eugene Gordlock,
a witness that repeatedly
asked the judge
to be recused
from the case,
was gunned down
just a few hours earlier.
We had the opportunity--
They shot him
right in our front yard!
My dear,
sweet little boy.
Pained words
of a grieving woman,
left all alone
in a city outraged
by these felons.
But no concrete
evidence of tampering.
And with Mr. Gordlock
now dead--
[gasp]
Do I fix your makeup
for you?
Come on, hack job.
Let's go to the do.
You know, so the captain
should have sent me out here
with 30, 40 men
to raze this bloody
get-out-of-jail party.
Instead,
I'm stuck here with you.
Well, he might
come out tonight.
As a matter of fact,
I'm pretty sure
he's gonna show up.
And, uh,
what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna bring him in.
[laughs]
You know,
you kill me, Soap.
Let's just say,
if you can make this happen,
why would you?
He does to those bastards
what me and you
can only fantasize about.
Hey, keep your
nose clean.
Yeah.
Sure thing, Pops.
[sniffing]
Hey,
Look, you know,
it's just, um--
Take it easy
in there, okay?
Nicky, what am I
gonna do?
Give the old guy
a heart attack?
Go on, beat it.
[Man]
Give meuno minuto.
You handled the
witness situation
perfectly.
No sweat, Uncle G.
You look great.
The hell I do.
I shit in a bag,
for Christ's sake.
Hey, saves you a trip
to the can, right?
You came to discuss
a private matter
down at the docks.
Right, yeah, Cristu Bulat.
I hear he's a sick fuck,
fresh off the boat.
Cristu's bringing in
a shipment,
needs a safe port.
I've arranged for
my Customs guy Simmons
to be on that night.
The union boys will
be there to unload.
Our cut's 10 mil.
We won't break a sweat.
10 mil?
Fuck's
Cristu shipping?
I don't know.
Some kind of
biological package.
A biological package.
I fucking knew it.
Probably going after
the ragheads in Queens.
Cristu's guaranteed
it's leaving the city.
We don't touch
that kind of shit.
In case your memory's going
along with the rest
of your bodily functions,
you might like to remember
I'm the top earner
around here.
I'm not stupid.
Stupido?
You're as shithouse
crazy as your brother,
Loony Bin Jim.
I should have had
the both of you
locked away!
One more word
about my brother,
I swear to Christ, I'll--
[guns cocked]
You heard a word.
You make one move,
you greasy fuck.
Hey, let's just all
calm down here, okay?
I put on a big spread
out here.
So come on, boys.
Eat up.
We're not fuckin' eating
with that old shitbag,
you understand?
Pittsy, pour me a drink.
[footsteps running]
[groans, bones crack]
Mangiare. Mangiare.
Mangiare.
Mangiare!
Eh!Che cosa fai?
[speaks Italian]
What the fuck?
[Woman]
What is this?
[crack, squish]
[crack, crack]
[screams]
[crack]
Aah!
Let's go.
[roaring]
Ugh.
[groans]
Aah!
All right,
let's split up.
Well, shouldn't we
wait for backup?
Police! Freeze.
Listen, Billy Russoti's
getting away.
Silver Rover.
You might want to head
down to the docks first.
[sirens approaching]
Fu--
Oh!
Shit, that hurts.
[spits]
Well, what happened
to you?
Your Punisher.
He disarmed me,
held me at gunpoint,
then he stole
our damn ride.
And where the hell
were you, huh?
I knew he would come.
Hey, let me get
your statement.
Come on, Saffiotti,
tell me everything--
How'd it go down?
Huh? Huh?
[thunder]
[buzzer]
[sniffling]
[crack]
Uhh!
[sniffs]
Ha, ha. Got ya.
Hey! Hey!
[laughing]
Ha ha ha!
[Man on tape]
I'm real sorry about
your family, Bill.
[Bill]
Oh, well, maybe it's
a blessing in disguise.
Why?
Well, it's time for me
to take over anyway.
Thanks to The Punisher,
I won't even get
my fucking hands dirty.
[laughs]
Ah, here's your bust in.
The fuck's he doing here?
Relax.
I asked him to come.
Ah, my man.
How are ya doing?
Who the fuck
are thesefinocchs?
These are a couple
of me colleagues.
They are very, very
gifted delivery men.
No mountain too high,
no river too deep.
[laughs]
Woo!
All right, all right,
all right.
Enough. Pittsy,
get me some money.
Time to go to work.
Running a little low, boss.
You just picked up 200k
from a Luciano
construction site.
I had to launder it through
the Pussycat Lounge,
like you told me.
Remember?
Well, bring it back.
Tomorrow.
You got it, boss.
Here. There's 20 rolls
of hundreds.
It's a grand each,
all counted.
Head for the port,
do your monkey thing.
Get over
the security fence.
Hand out the money.
Oh! Where the fuck
are you going?
Um, would it be all right,
if I took the roof
instead of the jar?
Whatever.
You're a fucking saint.
[laughs]
Hoo!
Ha!
[electronic pulse]
[click]
Ow.
Hey. What's the matter?
Aw, fuck.
What the fuck was that?
Agent down! Repeat!
Agent down! Fuck.
I'll check it out, boss.
[yelps]
Pops!
No.
I'll take care of it.
You get the guards.
[choking]
Pittsy!
[gasping]
[screaming]
[cursing, stammering]
Fuck you, Castle!
[yelling continues]
[engines start]
Fuck you, man!
Fuck you, Castle,
you fuckin'--
Fuck you, Castle! Fuck--
[shouting continues]
Fuck out of my fucking face!
Fuck! Pittsy!
Pittsy! Pittsy! Augh!
[Ink]
There he is!
[Man]
FBI! Drop your weapons!
Oh, shit. Shit!
You two up the stairs!
Get one on me!
Don't move! FBI!
Leave your weapons down!
[clattering]
[Man]
We got a live one!
[distant shouting]
[moaning]
Billy the Beaut!
[distant man]
Yo! Did you say
Billy the Beaut?
[groaning]
Not any more, huh?
I doubt
if he'll live.
[police radio chatter]
Wait a minute.
[police radio]
Might be Nicolas
Donatelli, Jr.
[chatter continues]
[Man]
The Lord is
compassion and love,
slow to anger
and rich in mercy.
He does not treat us
according to our sins,
nor repay us according
to our faults.
As parents have compassion
on their children,
the Lord has pity
on those who fear Him.
For He knows
of what we are made.
He remembers
that we are dust.
As for us, our days
are like grass.
We flower like
the flower of the field.
The wind blows,
and we are gone.
And our place
never sees us again.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Who compromised
Donatelli? Hmm?
Calm down, Budiansky.
Wasn't anybody's fault.
None of us could foresee
Frank Castle opening up
hunting season
onla Cosa Nostra.
Come on.
Look. Donatelli
sent us a message.
He said something big
was gonna happen.
He asked for
homeland security.
We've been running 24-hour
surveillance on Russoti.
And just as we were
about to find out what
the fuck is happening,
Donatelli got shot.
Believe me.
No one's more pissed off
about it than I am.
How is it we're not
all over Frank Castle?
Because we have a real
national security threat.
And the last time I checked,
that tops trying to nab
some crazed vigilante.
[opens door]
Go.
[engine starts]
[door closes]
Hey.
I'm gonna get
this guy, Angie.
I promise you.
[spits]
[horns honking]
I heard the bureau was
sending a babysitter.
Liaison
30 years on the force,
I still don't know
what that word means.
We have a certain way of
doing things around here,
Special Agent Budiansky.
Like letting mass
murderers run free?
Four years, this Punisher's
been wreaking havoc.
And you haven't once
caught a break.
I'm always deep in shit around
here, as you can plainly see.
Your buddies from
the Bureau told me
this city is under some
kind of terror threat.
New Yorkers are a bit
sensitive about that,
if you know what I mean.
I've got all my men
trying to find out
what your late colleague came
across when he went under.
Maybe if you Feds
allowed us lowly cops in
on your undercover
operations once in a while,
all of this could have
been avoided.
With all due respect,
Captain,
that...
is bullshit!
What if it had been
your man lying there, huh?
In a pool of his own blood?
You Krispy Kreme
motherfuckers
would be beating down
every door in this city.
Captain. Captain,
you know what?
The, uh, Punisher
task force, uh,
could use an extra man.
Hm.
Room 12.
The basement.
[door opens, closes]
Ah. Agent, uh,
Budiansky?
I get that right?
Captain told me
you were coming in.
Welcome to the
Punisher task force.
I'm Detective Martin Soap.
Pleasure.
Make yourself at home.
You have a degree in
behavioral psychology.
Surprised?
That's okay.
Most people are.
So, what do you
actually do here?
Here?
Mm-hmm.
This is ground zero.
I've shadowed his every step
for the last five years.
I've documented every murder
that fit his profile.
And I've collected intelligence
on all known associates.
Take a look at this.
Six years ago,
Frank Castle was a
special forces instructor.
Mm-hmm.
And a simple family man.
One day, he takes his wife
and kids for a picnic.
And by chance, or fate,
depending on what
you believe in,
they witnessed
a mob execution.
When they
were discovered--
[projector click]
But Castle survived.
[click]
Since then,
he's been taking down
one crime family
after another.
I'm really close,
Budiansky.
Only thing
getting in my way
is some bad luck.
But I have a feeling
that's about to change.
You know, I've been waiting
for someone like you.
Take a look at
some of the case files.
Get the lay of the land.
I'll get us a pie
from Milano's.
Best pizza in the city.
Which drawer?
What?
The alleged
Punisher murders.
All of them.
[sighs]
What do you want, Micro?
You ever heard of
JihadiBlogger.com?
I'm posing as a one-armed
Wahabi warrior
who took a crap in a cave
next to bin Laden.
I think I can score you
a couple of rocket launchers.
What do you want?
I haven't seen you
in a while.
Brought you some treats!
It's gun show season
in Virginia.
No background checks.
No problems.
That's too much, Frank.
Call it a
retirement package.
[zippers zip]
Look, I know this thing
with the Fed is eating
you up inside,
but that doesn't mean
you pack up your tent.
We all make mistakes,
Frank.
You're fighting a war
against the assholes
who slip
through the raindrops,
who get away with it.
In any war, there's
collateral damage.
You know that.
Collateral damage.
I killed an agent
in the field.
One of the good guys.
He had a family.
You didn't know.
[sighs]
I fucked up, Micro.
Now please.
Just leave me alone.
[Man]
Where the fuck's Nicky?
He, uh,
didn't make it.
Nicky was a fucking rat.
For the Feds.
What about my money?
We already went to his
place and tore it apart.
No sign of a safety
deposit key or nothing.
Well, has he got
any next of kin?
Somebody to carry on
the family name?
Yeah. Paper
said something
about a wife
and a little girl.
Good.
Let's look there.
Got it.
[door opens]
Hey, Doc!
Where you been?
Am I glad to see you!
Hi, Billy.
Should have seen those
fucking brascioles
at the clinic.
Must have bought their
fucking medical degrees
off the internet.
How the heck did you
end up at a free clinic?
Insurance said
I missed a payment.
Can you fucking
believe that?
Okay. Um,
before we do this,
I need you to understand
the severity of your injuries
when you arrived here.
Statistically speaking,
you shouldn't have been
able to survive this.
Well, that's
why I'm here, Doc.
I have the best plastic
surgeon in all of New York.
Your facial muscles,
tendons,
bone structure,
everything--
it was destroyed.
And there wasn't a single
square inch of skin
left intact.
Just take it off
already.
Okay. Uh,
let's do this.
[clears throat]
I'm gonna need you to
sit forward a little bit.
All right.
[whispering]
Okay.
Polymers.
Strategically-placed
alloy plates.
And just a little bit
of horse hide.
[Billy]
Little bit of what?
[vomiting]
[gasps]
I need to talk
to my doctor alone.
Yeah. Yeah.
Of course, Billy.
Uh--
What the fuck's
the matter with you?
You can't fucking
control yourself?
You know how sensitive
he is about his looks!
I'm sorry, Pop.
It's just--
have you ever seen
anything so--
Just shut the fuck up!
[knock on door]
You okay, boss?
Much better, thanks.
I'll be in the car.
No more distractions.
We need to focus
on my goals.
1...
we need to get
my money back.
2, we're gonna get
rid of Frank Castle.
But he took out,
like, 30 of us.
I mean, how are we
gonna kill him
before he'll kill us?
My brother will
take care of that.
Loony Bin Jim?
Shut the fuck up!
His name is James,
not Loony Bin Jim.
Not LBJ. James.
I'm sorry.
It's a good idea.
Really. It is.
[Pittsy]
Don't mind him.
He doesn't think
before he talks.
Just like his mother.
Sorry about that,
Billy.
Billy is dead.
From now on...
you call me Jigsaw.
[church bell rings]
[ringing continues]
[distant moaning, wailing]
[distant laughing, shouting]
[loud wailing]
How are we doing today,
Loony Bin Jim?
Mmm!
Yummy, yummy.
Ahhh. So good...
[banging on door]
What?
[Man] Doctor Faznar.
Open up!
Yes, Doctor.
[crack]
[thud]
Billy?
Is that you?
It is.
You look fantastic,
brother.
Ink. Cut these off.
Now.
[clink]
Pittsy, go open the doors
of every other cell.
Lead everybody
out the front door.
Sure thing, Billy.
Jigsaw.
I'll take care of
this guy.
Oh, no, brother.
Fatso's mine.
Of course.
I'm gonna get my
applesauce back.
Did you know--
[sniffs]
...kidneys and applesauce
are a delicacy in Sweden?
Did you know that?
Yes.
Yummy, yummy, yummy
in my tummy, tummy, tummy.
[yelling]
[laughing]
[flesh tearing]
[screaming]
Uh, what do you say, Boss?
Stuff might come in handy.
What for?
Well, uh,
in case he starts, you know,
not feeling so good.
[screams]
[grunting]
Looks like he's doing
just great.
[grunting continues]
[flesh tearing]
[yells]
Psst.
You're in my light.
For the next time
someone gets in your light.
Step the fuck away
from my little girl!
Mom, that's a Dad word.
Go inside, Grace.
You're messing with
the wrong family
on the wrong day, asshole.
You.
You're...
What are you doing here?
What makes you think
you can come here?
You'll scare the girl.
Shut up!
Just shut your mouth!
I'm sorry.
I said shut up!
What's this?
Something to help out.
No.
No, you don't
get to do that.
You don't get to shoot
my husband in cold blood
and then stop at the ATM.
It's for your daughter.
This is what you deserve.
What you did to Nick.
Who punishes you?
He taught you how to shoot.
A good agent
keeps his family safe.
But he couldn't
always be here.
He took you out to the range,
showed you what to do.
This is where you do it.
Squeeze.
Don't pull.
[Grace]
I can't find my red pen.
Mom, I need it.
Take it.
Is this it, Boss?
Yeah.
Nice, brother.
Is it yours?
Not yet.
Old Cesare used to rent it
to screw hookers.
Let's go inside before
I freeze my fucking balls off.
[sigh]
What's the matter, Billy?
Just when I think
I'm okay, I--
I see my reflection
somewhere, and...
I look horrible.
No.
What has he done to me?
Ohh.
[crying]
No, no, no. Don't.
Don't cry, brother.
Everything is going
to be all right.
I promise you two things:
1, I will find Castle,
and I will kill him
slowly and painfully.
And 2,
you will never ever
have to look
at your reflection again
as long as you're with me.
[sob]
[yelling]
[groaning]
[yells]
[yelling]
[laughing]
[speaking
native language]
You're not in Transylvania
anymore, Cristu.
We don't talk Vampire.
It's Russian.
[Russian]
My man is concerned.
If Punisher can do this
to your face,
what might he do
to our deal?
The tongue stretches further
than most people think.
Ask your man how he's
going to talk that shit
when I pull it
from his mouth.
[shouts in Russian]
[Russian]
Enough. The Punisher
is not a problem.
The docks are mine.
My looks have nothing
to do with this.
Everybody,
from the local security
to International Customs,
is in my pocket.
Quite frankly,
this job doesn't get done
without me.
[Russian]
Is concise.
[spits]
[laughs]
[laughing]
Step back, motherfucker!
Fuck off!
I'll blow your fucking--
[shouts in Russian]
My most sincere apologies.
My father always say
"Never insult your host."
Sounds like
a reasonable man.
You don't know of my father.
Three days.
It has to be 12 million.
We agree on 10.
We both know
that this biological shit
you're bringing in
isn't leaving the city.
You're selling it
to the rag-heads in Queens.
The ports have been crawling
with suits from Homeland,
and they take a lot of payola
to keep it quiet.
Always knew you'd be
a good boss,
Billy.
Thanks, brother.
[door buzzer buzzes]
Latin Kings.
[Micro]
Let him go, Frank.
You know
this piece of shit?
Ex-piece of shit.
Yeah.
He's a regular choirboy.
Fuck you, cracker.
Language.
It's a genius racket.
You know how the cops are always
running those gun buy-backs?
Except they never work.
Because what banger
is going to trust a cop, right?
Well, these drive-by
whack jobs,
they just love Carlos here.
They get one look
at that ink,
and they know he's for real.
We get the guns
off the street...
to you.
Never once seen a banger
that could quit.
Too fucking stupid.
He's straight, Frank.
Hey, Mom,
Frank's here.
He says eat up. Huh?
How's she doing?
Yeah, well,
as long as she's got
her cooking shows,
she's good.
It's the only thing
she notices.
But, hey,
that's something, right?
Listen, I--
I just came down to tell you
that I'm going out of town
for a while.
Out of town?
[chuckles]
[snorting laughter]
I'm sorry.
Frank, I--
I never thought
of The Punisher,
you know,
taking a long weekend.
I'm not planning
on coming back.
So I take it things
didn't go so well
at the Donatelli home.
Are you aware that
Billy Russoti survived?
I heard.
Let the cops
take care of him.
You and I know
they got nothing on him.
Their hands are tied.
This is where
The Punisher comes in.
This is why I believe in you,
why I've supported you
all these years.
Do you want me to tell you
when something happens
to Mrs. Donatelli
and her daughter?
Because that's
what's going to happen.
You don't think he's going
to go for revenge?
It's not a question of if,
it's a matter of when.
[whirrs]
Pull a couple of Berettas.
For what?
3, 2, 1.
Rusotti's the last one.
Then I'm done.
From your lips
to God's ears.
You know where
I can find him?
I don't have a fix on him.
You wiped out
all of his associates
that are known to me.
I saw him
with some new guys.
Leader was black,
dreadlocks.
Did some kind of acrobatic
stuff over the roofs.
That's Maginty
and his Urban Free Flow gang.
He's a mean motherfucker.
He's on a constant
meth high.
Well, come on.
You want to find
this guy or not?
You boys play nice.
I've been looking
for you.
Agent Budiansky.
Take a load off.
I need to go see Castle.
Where do I find him?
Rats. You know,
he just left.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You know
what I'd like to do?
I'd like to sit in my car
and listen to the CB radio
and follow the crime--
Might just run into him.
I mean, it's never worked
for me in five years,
but I'm not the luckiest guy
on the planet, you know.
Let's go through
the back door.
[glass shattering]
[door opens]
[rock]
Maginty and his boys
are planning to hit
a convenience store
on 45th and 2nd.
[laughter]
Whoo!
[alarm blaring]
[siren blaring]
[laughs]
Whoo!
[laughing]
[Man on radio]
Suspects are armed
and dangerous.
I repeat, suspects
are armed and dangerous.
Let's do this.
Really?
Just drive the car.
[engine starts]
Fly! Fly!
[yells]
Whoo!
[laughing]
[yelling]
[laughs]
[gunshot]
Aw, fuck!
Fuck!
[screams]
Ohhh!
Please, please.
Don't kill me.
Russoti. Where is he?
Yeah, man, Jigsaw.
I was just with him.
He was supposed to give us
some dope for a job.
But turns out--
[groans]--
he don't have any anymore.
He forgot he gave
a whole bunch
to that FBI bastard!
So he went to go see
Donatelli's wee bitch
to get it back.
Something for something,
Mr. Punisher, sir.
So when did Donatelli
go undercover?
We were partners
in Narcotics.
Unfortunately, most of
the blow we confiscated
ended up in my nose.
Internal Affairs tried
to get Nicky to rat me out.
He wouldn't,
so they sent him
undercover.
He's dead because of me.
So you still skiing
the old Alps?
No.
That's in the past.
[cries out]
Holy shit!
[gurgling]
[sniffs]
Drive around.
Meet me on the other side.
Mommy!
Boo.
Hello, Mrs. Donatelli.
Or will you be calling yourself
"Miss" from now on?
What do you want from us?
I'm looking for my money
which your rat of a husband
stole from me.
We don't have it.
I swear to God.
How about you,
sweet cheeks?
Would you also like to swear
on an imaginary friend?
[whimpers]
Make sure
they don't move.
You look for the money.
Come here, kid.
Freeze, asshole!
You're under arrest.
Stay out of my way.
[muffled muttering]
[coughing]
Listen to me.
Russoti is heading
to the Donatelli house.
He's probably
already there.
[phone beeping]
You have to let me go.
You have the right
to shut the fuck up!
[grunting]
Mommy.
[grunting continues]
[crash]
Yeah!
[laughing]
[dogs barking]
Damn it.
Cops.
[doorbell rings]
Evening, Officers.
Is everything
okay in there?
No.
Everything is not okay.
Follow me.
Officer.
Oh, no, you don't!
Oh.
[laughing]
Well, well, well.
This day was bound to come
sooner or later, wasn't it?
Have you heard back
from the patrol car?
Soap.
Hmm?
Oh. I tried
a couple times.
There was no answer.
Fuck.
Listen, we got to get
out of here
before more pigs arrive.
Where is my fucking money?
No!
My husband has a safe
upstairs in the bedroom.
I don't know if it's there,
but I can give you
the combination.
10-12-1965.
Oh, how cute.
Is that your
dead husband's birthday?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Hey.
Let me help you.
Get him to the station.
You bet.
[door opens]
Let me out.
You know, Frank,
throwing you a tip
now and again is one thing,
password to the crime
database is another,
but letting you go?
Soap.
Fine.
[bones cracking]
How you doing?
[gun clatters on floor]
[laughs]
19.
Fuck!
[laughs]
Fuck that--
[voice box whines]
[laughs]
[whimpering]
[distant clattering]
[glass shatters]
[dogs barking]
What was that?
Go check it out.
What the fuck
you waiting for, Christmas?
Now, you, sit down.
[Budiansky]
I'm calling this in.
Put your hands
behind your back.
God damn it, Castle!
Where do you think
you're going?
Castle!
[gunfire]
I repeat,
request immediate backup.
[gunfire continues]
Don't worry. I'm here.
Give me your fucking gun!
Fuck!
Stay right where you
fucking are!
We did it, Budiansky.
You mind
explaining to me
how a handcuffed criminal
escapes custody
from the back of
your locked car?
That Castle's
a slippery one.
You'll be safe here.
We can manage on our own.
Just until we know
Russoti's been arrested.
[sighs] Grace.
Grace, we're
leaving soon, honey.
She's smart.
Go ahead. Open it.
It, um, belonged
to my daughter.
Here.
["Cradle Song"]
Wow.
Put that down, honey.
It was, um,
Lisa's favorite toy.
She got so angry
when her little brother
used to hide it from her.
Does she care
if I play with it?
No.
[police radio chatter]
[siren]
You're gonna fry for killing
two of my officers, Billy.
I want a lawyer.
Oh, you'll get
your fucking lawyer.
But no lawyer's gonna
get you out of this one,
you ugly piece of shit.
[snickering]
[chatter]
Agent Miller,
what are you doing here?
Russoti.
What's he got to do
with the Bureau?
The case Donatelli
was working on.
It seems he's got some intel.
He wants to make a deal.
Anyone know where he is
right now?
Just brought him into
the observation room.
Good.
Yeah.
Captain Ross.
Agent Miller
for the Bureau.
I believe
you've been informed
I'll be taking over this?
This perp killed
two of my officers
and terrorized
a widow and child
of one of your agents.
You keep that
in mind, Miller.
You're lucky
I came to you with this.
But then I'm a patriot,
just like you.
I shit red, white,
and blue.
This reason you came to me
is because you got caught.
So don't insult
my intelligence, okay?
You tell me what you know.
If it's any good,
I'll recommend
life without parole.
This deal
is going down tonight.
I know when
and I know where.
So you're gonna give me
and my brother here
the immunity and the money.
Of you're gonna
have to explain to
Wolf Fucking Blitzer
why you had the lead
on the thing that killed
half the fucking city
and you didn't do
a goddamn thing about it.
Rawr.
I'll be right back.
Oh, and Miller?
There's just one
other little thing.
Wow.
Happy?
[loud buzzing]
[Men shouting]
Go, go, go, go, go!
Homeland Security!
Put your weapons
on the ground!
[speaking Russian]
You're fucking dead men.
My father will kill you.
Hear me?
My father serve your head
on fucking silver platter.
[spits]
[laughs]
Agent Miller.
As agreed.
The other condition
of our agreement?
Clear the area.
I hope to God he finds you
and you get what you deserve.
How long was I--
A long time.
You should eat.
Yuck.
Grace.
What is it?
Egg and cheese MREs.
It's all I have.
What's an MRE?
Meal, ready to eat.
Military food.
It's great for people
who can't cook.
Look, Grace, this one
came with Chuckles.
It's, um,
the best one to get.
Not exactly
a balanced breakfast.
Out of practice.
[metal clanging]
Not one more step.
Where's Micro?
His mother
isn't feeling well.
He didn't want
to leave her.
Damn it!
I need to talk to him.
This is Carlos.
He's a...friend of mine.
He's gonna hang while
I take care of some things.
Hi, Carlos.
I'm Grace.
Hey, little girl.
We're gonna be
homies, right?
[laughs] Yeah.
We're gonna be tight.
This will all be
over soon.
Then you can go.
Don't go.
I need you alert.
Don't make me
regret this.
[hard rock]
[honking]
She's wearin' dresses
on the borderline
That was fun.
Now let's go kill Castle
in his miserable hole.
No, not yet.
We're gonna have
ourselves a little
bit of fun with this.
Next time
he has to face us
and a fucking army.
Where do we get
the army from?
Just like Uncle Sam, bro.
We recruit in
troubled neighborhoods,
offer 100 grand towards
a college education
they'll never get,
and promise nobody
ever has to go to Iraq.
Just as long
as I get to kill Castle.
Don't worry, brother.
You will.
Just make damn sure
this time he don't
come back breathing.
[muffled shouting]
[Carlos laughing,
Grace giggling]
[Carlos singing in Spanish]
Boo!
[screaming]
Hello, sports fans.
And how are you today,
my friend?
Run! Get out of here!
Hey. I axed you a question.
Run!
[groaning]
[gasping]
Aah!
You don't answer.
Guess I'll have to
axe it again.
[James]
Here I come!
[tires screeching,
honking]
[car alarm beeping]
[muffled shouting]
[chuckles]
Good.
Bring 'em upstairs.
Meet me back down here.
Let's see if we can talk
a few poor bastards
into signing up.
[groaning]
Where are they?
[gasping]
I tried.
I swear I tried.
God damn it!
Don't die on me.
[groaning, coughing]
I'm bleeding out.
I've seen this show
before.
Shut up, kid.
You're gonna be fine.
It hurts real bad.
Hurts real bad, Frank.
Don't let me die
like this, man.
Not like this.
[gasping]
See you in hell.
I see you anywhere
near hell,
I'll kick your ass out.
[gunshot]
I haven't seen you
in ages, Frank.
Whatever it is,
it must be pretty bad.
Maybe I'm just here
to see an old friend, Mike.
Yeah, right.
I haven't seen you since--
The funeral.
I know.
I've been reading
about you.
You've been a long way
from the seminary,
my friend.
I don't even remember that
as part of my life.
Why do you do this?
Somebody has to punish
the corrupt.
For in the same way
you judge others,
you will be judged.
And with the measure
you use,
it will be measured
to you.
Matthew...7:2.
I'm okay with that.
God be with you, Frank.
Sometimes I'd like to
get my hands on God.
Interesting choice
for a meeting place.
Didn't take you for
a religious man, Castle.
Yeah, well,
an eye for an eye.
If I remember right,
they're not called
the Ten Suggestions.
Russoti's got
Angela and Grace.
How?
Doesn't matter.
Well, maybe if you put them
in protective custody
like you should have,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
They'd be dead.
The law can't
touch 'em, Castle.
Total immunity.
Unless you've got a videotape
of Russoti taking them.
Can't even give them
a parking ticket.
It's a fucked up system
you're sworn to protect.
Never said it was perfect.
He wants me
in exchange for them.
I need you
to secure the trade.
Okay.
But I'm doing this
by the book.
What book do you think
they're going by, huh?
I took an oath, Castle.
There are laws.
No official
police procedure.
You wanna come along,
leave your badge at home.
I have to think about it.
Clock's ticking.
[rap]
Oh, ho, gentlemen.
Gentlemen, relax.
We're looking
for a few good men.
And we'd like to offer you
the opportunity
to be...
all that you can be.
Now, we've all suffered loss
at the hands
of the Punisher.
And because we don't
look like everybody else,
and because we don't
act like everybody else,
nobody does
a goddamn thing about it.
Well, I say
he ain't the only one
can take the law
into his own hands.
So if you're as sick
of this cocksucker as I am,
raise your armies.
You'll be well paid.
You'll be well armed.
And at the end of it,
the Punisher will be dead!
[Men]
Boo-yah!
Hey, it's Budiansky.
Just in time
for happy hour.
You need to come with me.
Where to?
Your partner,
Frank Castle,
needs help.
I think "partner"
is a little bit
of an exaggeration.
How'd you know?
Well, usually, unless
you've arrested Houdini,
a handcuffed criminal
does not escape that easily.
[laughs]
You know, you're not
as stupid as you--
I didn't say that.
Who we looking for?
Cristu's father.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
[chatter in Russian]
What?
We're looking for Tiberiu,
Cristu's father.
Why?
If I were Tiberiu,
I'd probably want to find
the man who was responsible
for sending my son to prison,
for the rest of his life.
And how would you
do that?
I'd tell him when
and where to find him.
What do you want from it?
I don't like him.
I want him taken care of.
No worries, my friend.
All right.
Lock and load.
Here they are.
Oh, boy.
[siren in distance]
[mumbling, growling]
Take it easy, James.
He'll be here.
[loud knocking]
You get it.
Fuck that.
I'll get it.
What you looking for?
I'm here to see
the Jigsaw.
You out of luck.
No Jigsaw here.
I'm here
for the Punisher party.
Who's the old man?
That's Cristu's father.
Old Country
genocidal maniac.
Figured he'd stir up
a shit storm for us.
The cops'll
be all over this place
once the fireworks start.
Wouldn't worry
about that.
I called in
a explosives department.
Construction crew.
Said we'd be blasting
dynamite all night.
So...what's the plan?
I'm going in
to get them.
You call that a plan?
It's all I need.
Well, I'm going in
with you.
Never took the time
to think about
where I was headed.
I'm far down
that road.
You're not going there.
Oh, Jesus.
Thanks, Frank.
You know he's gonna
take it out on me
when he wakes up.
If you don't hear gunfire
for longer
than five minutes,
and the girls are not here,
set him loose.
[gunfire continues]
[gunfire stops]
Yaah!
[Man]
Come on, get him!
Go, go, go!
[gun cocks,
Man whispers]
[gasps]
It's time.
James! Be careful.
[growling]
Oh, for fuck's sake.
[groans]
Won't be replacing
that son of yours
any time soon.
[groans]
Blood in the urine.
Early indicator
of kidney failure.
You should be seeing
double right about now.
[cracking]
[groans]
That would be
a torn meniscus.
[cracking]
Aah!
[groaning]
[roaring]
Aah!
James.
Gun!
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
[laughing]
Mom?
[gasping]
Please, help us.
Shut the fuck up.
Come on, Castle.
Don't be shy.
Throw down your gun.
Die, you bastard.
No!
James, that's no way
to punish the Punisher.
[groans]
[laughter]
Nice shooter.
Aah!
[groans]
Catch.
Let's play a game.
What do you say?
You got one round
left in there.
You shoot
one of these two,
I'll let the other one
go free.
What do you say, Frank?
Who's it to be?
Your fat friend
right here
or that nice little piece
of jailbait over there?
Burn in hell.
Okay.
Then they both die.
Frank!
She's a kid.
Shoot me.
Okay, fuck it.
Kill her first.
No!
Stop!
He's made a decision.
It's not looking
too good for you, fatso.
After 3, Castle.
1...2...
You won't
feel a thing, Micro.
3!
Aah! God!
Frank!
Get out.
Fuck you.
Let me put you
out of my misery.
[screaming, gurgling]
This is just the beginning.
[coughing]
You okay?
Where's Castle?
Still inside.
And Micro?
[gasping]
Frank!
Frank, are you okay?
You better
get out of here.
Yeah. Come on, Frank.
I'll buy you a drink.
Wait. Wait.
My husband, Nicky,
we talked about you.
Argued about you.
He said you were
one of the good guys.
[bell ringing]
You know, buddy,
maybe it's time
to quit now, huh?
I mean, you must
get tired of this, right?
You know, I think you got
all the criminals in town.
If there are any left,
they've got to at least
consider rehabilitation.
I mean, contrary
to popular belief,
people can change.
I guess what I'm saying is
I'm just personally
not a fan
of the death penalty.
Frank?
Where'd he go?
Hey.
Give me your
fucking wallet,
motherfucker.
You're kidding,
right?
Do I look like
I'm fucking kidding?
Frank.
Give me your wallet!
Frank!
Do you want to die?
[electricity buzzing]
For the last time,
give me your wallet.
[gunshot]
Oh, God.
Now I've got brains
splattered all over me.
[hard rock]
Oh, one quick move
is flowing flesh and brain
Then we know
it's a bleeding heart
Suddenly flash
burned into your eyes
Bullet meets skull,
meet the end of your life
In the war zone
I stand alone
I drive it home
Yeah, spider crack mirror
on a jigsaw face
Planning up in his room
on a muzzled face
Another day in hell
And Jesus saves
But still will punish
although we'll survive
In the war zone
I stand alone
I drive it home
You can't see me,
you can't stop me
You can't kill me
You can't see me,
you can't stop me
You can't kill me
In the war zone
I stand alone
I drive it home
You can't see me,
you can't stop me
You can't kill me
You can't see me,
you can't stop me
You can't kill me
There must be something
Sworn to tear me down
Oh, yeah
My pain is building
Tearing me inside out
Oh, yeah
Will I finish last again
Here I wait
for this to end
I forced the pain
I struggle with
And I am open to you
I could turn
the other way
Take control
and make a change
Take me,
take me away
You can bend me,
I won't break
Things won't always
go your way
Take me,
take me away
I am scarred
to the bone
But I feel relieved
And you can't
take that away from me
What I'll never know
Is how you can be
so blind
To what I've seen
I will be the first
to try
By myself until I die
Take a chance
for myself
And I am open to you
I could
turn the other way
Take control
and make a change
Take me,
take me away
I could
turn the other way
Take control
and make a change
Some things
will never change
Take me,
take me away
You can bend me,
I won't break
Things won't always
go your way
Take me,
take me away
Oh
Check, check
Get the feelin'
These are the days
of revenge so sweet
Can you feel it?
There is a fear
in the air
That I've prayed for
for my whole life
Can you feel it?
And do you fear it?
And Malcolm was right
The hate that we've sown
has come home in the night
So wake up,
it's time to die
Can you feel it?
'Cause we've reached
the end of the lies
Holy Mother
of Columbine
Say a prayer for me
Blessed martyrs
of Palestine
Come and strike us down
Just take a look at
the papers and your leaders
They're killers
and they're liars
See what they do
in your name
To make the bodies
pile higher
Closed-Captioned By
Burbank, CAServices, Inc.